Oh my gosh, I'm back again.
Hello friends,
I'm back with another get ready with me
and
a product review
and I don't know, maybe something else.
We'll see.
But for now, I want to get this makeup
going because I have somewhere to be
soon.
Okay. So, first I'm going to start off
with my serum.
So, how is everybody doing?
Um, I'm still waiting on my
results from the doctor, but we'll see
how that goes.
I'll let you guys know.
Um, like I said, hopefully nothing
serious,
but
I am feeling a little bit better today.
Um, as far as my legs and my arms go,
but my back,
I had a really hard time sleeping last
night. So, I really didn't sleep until
this morning
and
now it's afternoon.
I mean, I've been up a while, but I've
already had coffee, breakfast, I just
had some scrambled eggs with cheese. I'm
just letting this dry right now. But
while we're doing that, I was thinking
about this. I need to start using my lip
glosses cuz I have so many and
they go bad if you don't use them.
Like they get funky.
But yeah, I'm just using this one here.
This is from the Dollar Tree.
Um
Still a little bit wet. I need one of
those fancy fans, right? [clears throat]
Um,
let's see.
I'll use this. Maybe
this ain't working. There we go.
I have these envelopes.
I guess these are
Forever stamped
envelopes.
I don't know. I'm going to have to mail
my mom's something and see if she gets
it.
Mail her a letter
cuz I've had these for years.
They came from my uncle.
He brought us a bunch of stuff when my
aunt passed away from Texas
and that was in there.
And I think I asked my mom about that
and I'm pretty sure she said
yes, those are forever stamp envelopes
and you could use them. So,
all right. Now I'm just going to use
some
I always forget what this is called.
Concealer
I use it all the time too. This is like
my number one thing.
I guess cuz I use it more as a
foundation
that I probably just think of it as that
and can't think of the real name.
But yeah, this is also from Dollar Tree.
Just use my
brush.
Veto, what are you doing, buddy?
wagging your tail.
There's nobody up there. He's looking up
at the bed cuz I have I threw a blanket
cuz the seat that I'm on I keep an extra
blanket on and I threw the blanket on
the bed
and he thinks it he probably thinks it's
Carl up there
but it's not.
Carl's out with his friend
outside.
So, today's a little bit cooler. It's
nice
for a change.
Okay, I'm just going to use
this kind of bronzer blush.
Um,
I was reading about um seroriatic
arthritis
because
like I said, I've been so sore
and I wasn't thinking it was arthritis
because
the doctor asked me, "Do your joints
hurt?" And I said, "Yeah." But I failed
to mention to her that my muscles really
hurt. Like my upper arms and my upper
legs.
Well, when I Googled about it, it said
that
when you have seroriatic arthritis
or maybe any arthritis, rheumatoid,
whatever, um that your
muscles can hurt as well
because
they're like making up for the lack of
your joints or whatever. So
yeah, I don't know too much about it,
but
I do know
that I don't want to take any harsh.
So, I do want to
change my diet and I have just recently
to see if I can nip this in the bud
because
yeah, this ain't no way to live. I'm in
so much pain
every day. At night when I lay down, in
the morning when I get up, it's
terrible.
And that was another symptom is if
you're like real achy when you get up.
Yes.
Well, yes, I am. [clears throat]
But yeah, I I hope I could control it
through diet and [clears throat] not
have to take anything
cuz I don't know. I I did um quite a
while ago actually
not like years or anything, but a few
months back I joined
the
seriotic
arthritis page
and
just to get some information.
And um
that's helping a lot too. Um some
feedback from people who deal with it
even though I don't I'm not diagnosed
with it. But I don't know. I think I
think that could be what's going on
because I do have the patch on my back.
I have pitting in my nails,
which is also a sign of seroriatic
arthritis
from what I've read.
And I know people say, "Quit googling
stuff." But guess what? That's what the
doctors do, too. They'll do it right in
front of you.
like my um hydrogenitis superior. One of
my doctors had no idea what that was.
So they Googled it right in front of me
and started reading about it, which was
fine. I mean,
it once was considered to be very rare,
but now more and more people are coming
forward that have it. So, because
people just didn't know what it was and
they were embarrassed to come forward
with it.
But now, oh yeah, I want to put a little
touch of eyeliner on,
but I don't want this video to be all
about that.
So,
look at these beautiful colors instead.
Um,
well,
maybe I should There's no purple in
here.
Or is there? That could be like a light
purple. I guess we'll just do this.
We'll try.
I think this is like a light to medium
purple.
Yes, it is.
But yes, it's very nice out today.
A nice change in the humidity anyways.
So,
I hear lots of people riding motorcycles
today and
all those fun things of summer.
I think it's next week we're supposed to
get a touch of fall.
That'll be nice. It's my favorite.
My favorite.
All right. Now, let's do some
mascara. I'm going to go in with
Let's see. Maybe not this one.
I'm going to go in with
I haven't used this one in a while. So,
oh, maybe because I can't open it.
Like the I'm going to have to have my
husband probably open this one.
There we go. I got it.
Hear that, Veto? I don't know what that
is. They might be cutting wood out back.
It sounds like
they just cut wood for um
just a backyard fire.
And
just for funs.
My mom on the other hand,
she has to have a lot of wood
delivered
because she has a wood burning stove in
upstate New York.
So for her it's essential,
for us it's [clears throat] just for
fun.
But it's nice having a wood burning
stove
cuz you don't got to pay those high gas
bills.
And then in the summer we got to pay pay
the high electric bills because of the
air conditioners.
Um, yeah, this one
seems like it's starting to dry out. So,
I'm glad I'm using it now, though,
because it's working. But
I should keep using this one for like my
everyday
until it's gone cuz
it is starting to dry out like I said.
Okay, so that's the makeup look. I did
straighten my hair today before I came
in here to do this.
And let's see.
So, product review.
This is from the Dollar Tree and it's
the Brazilian
Orchid. I think it is. I think I said
orchid orchard or something last time,
but I believe that says orchid.
Brazilian orchid body butter.
And it is in the scent
I have my glasses. What does that say?
Oh, orchid and sandalwood
scent.
So, I've been using this one. It's very
thick cuz it's a body butter. It smells
pretty good. At first I was like, hm, I
don't know. Like I thought it was too
strong of a smell. But I've been using
it and I use it on my psoriasis on my
back after my showers and it's really
good for that. And I've been using it on
my hands. I do have psoriasis on my
hands, too. And I've been doing a lot of
dishes lately, giving my hubby a break
because really my hands get really bad
in the winter, in the fall and winter I
think it is.
Um, and that's when he'll like do more
dishes and stuff too because my hands
get bad. So, but yeah, I'm really liking
this. I put it on my elbows.
because I do have the psoriasis on there
too.
But
okay,
so that's that. But yeah, I really like
this one. And
um I have the other one I'll have to
review with you guys another time cuz
it's not in here. So
let's see.
I'm just going to wear this ring today.
It matches.
Um okay. And that's that. And I'll see
you guys in a little bit.
>> [music]
[music]
>> So, I'm back upstairs in the house and I
forgot I was going to show you guys the
other day and I never got to it um this
good deal I got on some groceries. So,
I'm going to show you now. Okay. So,
first of all, this isn't nothing new,
but well, actually the Philly cheese
steak. We've had them before. We
normally don't get these ones, but I got
them because they did not have the
pepperoni ones available, but these are
still good. The Philly cheese steak
calzones from Aldi's. So, I picked up
two of those.
And those are just a simple meal. I keep
them in the freezer for when we just
need something
that, you know, quick.
if I didn't thaw any meat or anything
like that.
But then from Giant Eagle, I picked
these up. Um, this one is
the sweet sesame chicken. I picked up
two of those.
And then I picked up
two pineapple chicken ones. You see
there's a lot of protein in there.
There's only 290
calories there. 300 in these ones. And
they're a nice little meal. And then I
got one of the general
toos,
if that's how you pronounce that. Spicy
chicken. Um,
yeah, I picked these up because they
were five for $10, which is a great deal
for these. So that makes them two bucks
each. And normally I don't know how much
they are upwards of four or five dollar
each. So whenever I see these on sale
like that, I get them because they're
good. And they're the steamers. They
steam right up in the microwave
and they're very good. A nice little
meal
for a long day when you don't cook.
So yeah, as you seen, we were outside
for a little while with our friends and
we had a fire in the back. It smells so
good. It's actually blowing in the
window right now, which I love. And um
but yeah, now I'm going to eat a late
dinner. Um
just some leftover um chicken and rice.
So,
but yeah, I think I'm going to end this
vlog here and thank you for watching and
I will see you soon. Bye.